Ah, you're finally awake, slave Troyard.
Where am I?
You are in my castle, and you are safe now. Take your time and rest.
What happened? How did I get...
I remember being interrogated by Count Cruteo, but...
You have nothing more to fear from him. I have dealt with Count Cruteo.
My lord, are you saying... that you have killed Count Cruteo?
Your father is a man to whom I owe a great debt.
Accordingly, I am bound by honor to repay it.
A debt?
Fifteen years ago, when war broke out, I was given the assignment of landing on Earth as a scout for the Empire.
While there, I was caught in Heaven's fall and suffered massive, life-threatening injuries.
When the moon was sundered and the Earth's crust was deformed, there was no haven where any of us could turn for help.
When I was found by your father, Dr. Troyard, he did not even hesitate to help. My life was saved by his care.
Father did that?
And now I have seen just how deeply your loyalty to the princess runs.
I find it utterly admirable how you managed to conceal her survival so the assassins were not aware of the fact.
My lord, how did you know that Her Highness was alive?
Slain, you should understand that Count Cruteo is not a traitor.
He has proven his loyalty and truly meant his oath to the princess.
But that is not the case for me. I am the one who plotted every attempt against her, and I will kill her.
Huh?
I am the one who plotted every attempt against her.
Pay attention to your surroundings, and also don't forget your infrared, and keep a sharp lookout.
Yes, ma'am. Showing three bogeys, two o'clock.
But there's no IFF signal. Flagging is hostile. They're nearly in weapons range. Engaging now!
Wow, look at that. Yuko's really good. She's like a one-woman militia.
Yep, she's got pretty good instincts, no question about that. Are you here to get some practice in, too?
Come on. You know that I got assigned to the maintenance crew.
Well, for the moment, anyway.
Wait, you mean that there could possibly be an opening?
You have to remember, this is a war.
Why don't you let me try?
Hey, sniper girl, what's up?
I thought you said you haven't had any military training before.
I played a lot of games.
Hey, was one of them SimCat 10? That game's absolutely sick!
I'm only so-so at live drills, but I kick ass at that game.
I'm impressed you learned to pilot the real thing from a game.
Those Martians!
Can't tell by looking at them that they're not from Earth,
so there's no way to know till they come clean about it.
Inaho's been such a major jerk about this.
He knew who she was, and he wouldn't even tell his friends.
Well, I guess my baby brother is finally starting to grow up.
Would have been nice if he'd confided in his big sister, though.
Now that he's found a girl he really likes...
What?
Huh? What do you mean? What'd you just say?
Given the times we live in,
a Martian wouldn't exactly be met with open arms.
But if he had a real princess in his life,
that means we'd all be related to a family of royals.
Uh, whoa.
Is that really true? Is that what he's gonna do?
Come on now, romantic stuff and your brother?
He's not even smiling at her or anything.
He's just wearing the same standard grumpy look.
He's different now, completely.
You really think so?
I'm family. I always know what's going on.
I see when he's happy, or when he's depressed and low,
or when he's telling me a lie.
That is his on-cloud-nine face.
Sure about that?
Think about it.
My emotionless nerd brother listening to every word
coming out of a girl's mouth is not standard.
You got a point there.
Well, for him, it's the ultimate expression
of how much affection he feels.
Lord, Dr. Kaiska!
Permission to take a break now!
Go ahead.
Hey, wait for me!
So can I give it a try?
Sure, why not? Climb on in.
If you're sure you don't want to join the others.
Are you really able to tell?
When someone is lying to you?
Yeah, pretty much.
Like right now, for instance.
You're covering up something, aren't you?
A Martian.
And she's a princess, too.
Guys sure do love taking on a challenge, don't they?
Well, I wouldn't worry about it.
You've got as good a chance with him
as anybody else here does.
It makes me feel great that my little brother
is so popular with the girls.
This map shows the 26 landing castle drop points
confirmed by the UFV before contact was lost.
But there are 37 clans in the Mars Knights.
There's a possibility that other landing castles
have made Planet Ball.
And Intel suggests a possibility
their forays are mostly in urban areas.
Therefore, we can minimize the possibility
of enemy encounters by routing our flight
through low population areas
and at low altitude to avoid radar.
Commander Mizusaki.
Ma'am, would you like to know
why you have such difficulty getting a date?
Uh, yes.
Possibility, possibility, possibility.
If you do nothing but play it safe
when opportunity arises,
you'll likely never meet Mr. Wright.
I was given to understand
one should first form a bond, ma'am.
All right.
Let's go with your
I-want-to-make-steady-progress-toward-my-goal-without-any-excitement approach.
So then you don't approve?
I think it's a very safe and well-thought-out plan.
She doesn't like it.
Sim target destroyed.
Okay then, simulation's complete.
Ryei, isn't it?
Congrats.
You gamers have a pretty intense set of skills.
Increase the difficulty.
Listen, maybe we should just call it a day.
I'm fine.
Keep going.
Hmm.
Okay.
I'll throw in something we came up against a little while ago.
Try this out.
Begin simulation.
Thermal signature detected.
It's on my ten.
Target almost in range.
Watch it, Ryei.
Don't do that.
You'll overheat the gun barrel.
Ah!
Simulation terminated.
I'm sorry.
I made it too difficult, too quick.
Sorry if it threw you.
Warrant officer Kaiska.
Oh, hey, Dr. Yagurai.
How's that servo assist working out?
Want to do a little arm wrestling?
No, I don't think so.
Actually, I was hoping I could borrow your simulator program a little later.
Are you planning on going into combat now, Doc?
No, definitely not doing that.
I need it for a treatment plan.
Damn it to hell.
I can't believe it.
Our captain turns out to be your kid's sister, Huma Ray.
Well, that probably explains where she gets her guts.
Ryei, would you mind if we sat down to eat with you?
Suit yourself.
Your Terran food is wonderful.
Unusual and delicious dishes we don't have on verse.
Is that optical camouflage?
Huh?
Inaho's friend Nina was kind enough to allow me to borrow these for the time being.
She said it must not have been easy trying to walk through the ship in that dress.
Isn't she kind?
Excuse me, your highness.
These are for you.
Oh, just look at them.
Paper models of lovely Terran birds.
Thank you greatly.
I'll treasure them always.
That was more thoughtful than I would have expected from you commoners.
We shall make a point of this to his imperial majesty when we once again have peace between the earth and...
Martians are known to everyone as the enemy.
How can you stay so composed?
Even though they were plotting your death.
You're insane.
Mind your tongue!
How dare you say such a thing to her, royal highness!
And I thought we were on the same side.
Hey!
You come back here right now!
Oh, these Terrans are so uncivilized!
How are you feeling, okay?
Well, so far, I feel fine.
I recreated the scene based on what you described to me, Lieutenant.
I think it should be pretty close, but if I got something wrong, let me know, alright?
You really think this little gizmo can help?
P-T-S-D.
There's one treatment that worked pretty well for post-traumatic stress disorder.
It involved trying to recreate the incident that caused it and then reliving it over and over.
Go through a terrifying experience often enough and get acclimated to it, huh?
Well, we'll see how it goes.
Why don't we begin?
Yeah, alright.
And here we go.
Come on.
Even games look a lot more real than this these days.
That I wouldn't know.
But we're not playing a game.
Ah, you got this street flip from right to left.
I'll get that fixed for next time.
What is that down there?
That's your crewmate, Humoray.
Oh, come on now.
Give me a break.
I can tell you for a fact what's eating at me ain't a crash test dummy.
Hey, you gotta trust me.
Just be quiet and keep watching.
Come on, Doc.
Really?
Are you messing with me?
Wait a minute.
No, that's...
Marito!
What the hell is that?
Nobody said there'd be anything like that.
Hold it together.
We got that thing outnumbered.
Platoon commander to all tanks.
Attack formation!
What is that?
Marito!
That thing's doing this?
It flies?
Our shells, they're...
Marito!
Anti-gravity?
No!
The tanks have lost cause.
Humoray, we gotta get out!
I can't!
My legs are pinned!
Fire!
Humoray!
Marito!
Get me out, Marito!
Hurry, Marito!
Marito!
Shoot me!
Shoot!
Please!
Marito!
Hurry!
Shoot me, Marito!
No!
Oh!
Ah!
Whoa!
Ohh!
Oh!
Lieutenant, Lieutenant Marito, calm down. You're all right.
It's okay. You were just remembering the past. You're completely safe.
You're not on Tanegashima anymore.
Like hell, anyone is safe. We're all on the battlefield now.
I think that's enough for today.
Talk about pathetic. Scared by a crash test dummy in a simulation.
No, that's not it. What's getting to you is something a lot more serious.
The thing that's got you so upset is that you killed your friend.
This is wrong. Wrong. Wrong. It's just wrong.
Why did she reveal her identity? Why? Why is she so calm?
Why? Why? Why? Why is she alive?
Why am I alive?
What's the matter? Not hungry?
You do not have to worry. It contains no poison.
If I wanted you dead, it would have been done already.
Lord Sosbaum?
Yes.
Why are you so determined in waging a war against Earth?
It is a lord's duty to wage war, to continually expand his domain for the benefit of his vassals.
And is that the only reason?
It is, in fact, a great cause.
This meat, it is from a creature that flies through the air.
Yes, my lord. Actually, this particular bird is flightless.
It's unimaginable luxury to the greater population of Verse, who subsist on Krill and Chlorella.
I feel nothing but indignation towards the Terrans who so offhandedly sent them as emergency relief food.
My lord, this is not a luxury item. It is food tailored for space transport and preservation.
Agriculture is Earth's domain, blessed as it is with abundant water and air, living creatures.
But back on Father Verse, although thanks to Alt-Noah our technology is extremely advanced,
we have never developed agriculture.
There is no valid reason we should not seize the plentiful resources of this world.
But my lord, surely there is no need for Princess of Salem's life to be...
It is too late. The war is already set in motion.
Her Highness is a necessary sacrifice to the war.
But my lord, she is innocent!
She is royalty, and her very lineage is the crime of which she is guilty.
Fifteen years ago, the royal family whipped the knights into a frenzy and sent them against Earth.
For that they will pay, and their own dear flesh and blood will be the price.
Please, my lord, you must not kill her!
We are a people who are oppressed under a feudal system which is centered around Alt-Noah.
Our poor, shabby society looks with scorn upon a world with a vast history.
What a bunch of nonsense that is!
The royal family controls the masses by saying envy Earth, begrudge Earth, despise Earth.
It is natural that verse is so corrupt that only through invading Earth can its cause be maintained.
Your own injuries bear witness to that all too well.
The royal family chose the path of war, all just to maintain order.
And then, as a result of that war, we suffered Heaven's fall,
and my beloved fiancée, Orlaine, had her life taken!
This war is my vengeance.
This war is my appointed task.
Defy me, and there will be no mercy.
Even if you're the son to the man I owe my life.
I did fear some hostility, my lady, but thankfully that was not the case.
Yes, I am relieved that the people of Earth are so kind.
Perhaps they understand that you are not their enemy, but only another victim yourself.
Deep down, we are all fellow humans.
Our birthplaces may differ, yet we can still relate to each other.
Some of them are rude and quite strange, though.
Oh no! Apologies, my lady!
I forgot your new clothing!
I'll go fetch it at once!
How should you know the water?
I say it depends.
It depends.
I say it depends!
Oh, that was really very fast.
Oh, look.
Adel Ritzo, shouldn't you be with Salem?
Her name is not Salem.
It is Her Highness Princess's...
Oh, no, a drive error.
Output decreasing.
Switch to backup power.
Can't maintain altitude.
Rate of descent accelerating now.
Impact in 30 seconds.
All hands, brace for impact.
Jesus Christ.
He lasted for a few minutes.
That night.
The temperature let go.
Time to call to the staff 이렇게
Let the moon shine and we face it
When the moon is still bright
With the light
Like he's oh
Not out of light
Heart, the sun
Oh
A dash for crazy one